That damn superstar…
He was definitely
looking down on me
Hey, what's up?
Hyesung!
An article's up
Article?
You're the top
search keyword online
What?
Check it up now
[Shin Yoo-il is Dating]
Everyone's so excited
[1st Gay Actor Couple!]
I never expected this…
[Who's Lee Hyesung?]
It's unbelievable
[Shin Yoo-il Dating a Guy]
Wow
[Shin Yoo-il is Dating
Lee Hyesung]
[who acted Minhyung
in "My Crazy Family"]
Damn, I hate that photo
I should've taken some
fancy profile photo
Does that matter now?
Come to the office now
We're on fire!
[Yoon Soobin]
Oh no, I'm gonna
get an earful
The number you've
called is unavailable
Please leave a message
after the tone
[Shin Yoo-il is Dating]
Six months?
What a bullshit
Why don't you call him
from time to time?
He seems to like you
What are you
hesitating for?
Did he say that?
President Goo
said that